Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Activism, 1973-2000, Undated; 1; 11.35 cubic ft.
  - General Activism, 1975-2000, Undated; 1.1; 1.6 cubic ft.
    - New York State Activism, 1978-1995, Undated; 1.1.2; 0.3 cubic ft.
      - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center, 1992 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 50)
      - Lesbian and Gay Leadership Summit, 1994 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 51)
      - Mailings, 1982; 1991; 1992 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 52)
      - National Association of Social Workers, NYS Chapter, ca. 1989 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 53)
      - New York City Lesbian and Gay Funding Collaborative, 1995 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 54)
      - New York City Zoning Laws, 1995 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 55)
      - New York State Coalition Against Domestic Violence, 1989 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 56)
      - New York State Gay and Lesbian Lobby - Buttons, Undated (Box 30 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 7)
      - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby, 1986; 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 57)
      - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby - nameplate, Community Organizing, 1988 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 58)
      - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby - nametag, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 59)
      - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby Organizing Workshop, 1988 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 60)
      - New York Women Against Rape, ca. 1978 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 61)
      - News clippings, 1991; 1992; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 62)
      - Notes (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 63)
      - OUT: A Fund for Lesbian and Gay Liberation, 1990 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 64)
      - OUT in New York, 1994 (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 65)
      - Publications, 1987 (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
      - Radioactive Waste, public health, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 66)
      - Rallies, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 67)
      - Women Against Pornography, 1979; 1980; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 68)
      - Women's Resistance Exchange, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.2-New York State Activism), Folder 69)
    - Activism - Other, 1976-2000, Undated; 1.1.3; 1 cubic ft.
      This subseries includes political literature, news clippings, correspondence and mass mailings, reports, press releases and other publications.
      - Africa, 1986 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 70)
      - AIDS, 1985-1989; 1992; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 71)
      - AIDS Action Council, 1987 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 72)
      - Anti-Discrimination, 1993; 1994 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 73)
      - Anti-Gay and Lesbian Materials, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 74)
      - Awards, 1993 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 75)
      - Bisexuality, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 76)
      - Black Hills Alliance, 1980 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 77)
      - Christian Appalachian Project, 1994 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 78)
      - Civil Disobedience, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 79)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1995 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 80)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1990; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 81)
      - Developing Nations, 1979 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 82)
      - Energy, 1979 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 83)
      - Environmental Movement, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 84)
      - The Fairness Fund, 1987 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 85)
      - Freedom Socialist Party, 1986 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 86)
      - Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation, 1988; 1991; 1994; 1996 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 87)
      - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund, 1985; 1990; 1994 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 88)
      - Gay Community News, 1987 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 89)
      - Grenada, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 90)
      - Guerrilla Girls, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 91)
      - Hat - North Carolina Lesbian & Gay Pride March, Asheville, North Carolina, 1992 June 13 (Oversized 8, Folder 1)
      - Homelessness, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 92)
      - Human Rights, 1987; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 93)
      - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1991; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 94)
      - "Indian Roots of American Democracy", 1988 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 95)
      - International Lesbian Conference - buttons in French, 1986 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 96)
      - International Lesbian Conference, conference material, 1982-1986 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 97)
      - International Lesbian Conference, conference material, 1984-1985 (Oversized 4, Folder 5)
      - International Lesbian Conference - poster in French, 1986 (Oversized 2, Folder 16)
      - International Lesbian Conference - poster in French, 1986 (Oversized 2, Folder 17)
      - International Lesbian Conference Poster - LSIS-WICCE: Women's International Cross-Cultural Exchange, Geneva, Switzerland, Undated (Roll 2, Folder 1)
      - Iran-Contra, 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 98)
      - Jessie Jackson speech at Democratic National Convention and recording of The Phil Donahue Show episode concerning Tawana Brawley, 1988 (Vhs 1)
      - Labor Organization, 1991; 1992 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 99)
      - Ladies Against Women, 1980-1984; 1986; 1987; 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 100)
      - Ladies Against Women, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 6)
      - Ladies Against Women, Consciousness Lowering Kits, 1984 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 101)
      - Latin America/Mexico, 1982-1984; 1986-1989; Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 102)
      - Lesbian Families: Affirming Our Choices, 1988; 1989 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 103)
      - Lesbian & Gay Network/Mobilization for Survival, Undated (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 104)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 105)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1991-1995; 1998; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 1)
      - Lesbian Issues, 1978; 1983-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 2)
      - Mailings and Notes, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 3)
      - The Middle East, 1981; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 4)
      - Mississippi murders, 1994 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 5)
      - Montreal, Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 6)
      - National Coming Out Day, 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 7)
      - National Lesbian Mentorship Project, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 8)
      - National Organization for Women, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 9)
      - Native American Rights, 1980; 1984; 1986; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 10)
      - Ellen Nesbitt, 1986 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 11)
      - News clippings, 1986-1988; 1990-1991; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 12)
      - No Diet Day/Fat Activists, 1994; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 13)
      - North Carolina Lesbian and Gay Parade, 1986; 1987; 1991; 1992 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 14)
      - Not in Our Name, 1984 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 15)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 16)
      - Nuclear Weapons, 1986 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 17)
      - Nuclear Weapons/Radiation, 1979-1980; 1984-1985; 1987-1988; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 18)
      - Organizing and Internal Conflict, Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 19)
      - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays, Inc., 1988 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 20)
      - The Peace Movement, 1986; 1987; 1999; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 21)
      - People with Disabilities, 1990 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 22)
      - PETA, Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 23)
      - Politics, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 24)
      - Pornography Issues, Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 25)
      - Publications, 1979; 1981; 1983 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 26)
      - Publications, 1985 (Oversized 4, Folder 7)
      - Publications, 1985; 1987; 1988 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 27)
      - Publications, 1990; 1992; 1993; 1995; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 8)
      - Race Issues, 1981; 1983; 1990; 1992-1994; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 28)
      - Rallies and Marches, 1980; 1982; 1984-1985; 1988; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 29)
      - Rallies, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 9)
      - Resistance, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 30)
      - San Diego Lesbian and Gay Pride, 1995 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 31)
      - Sharon Kowalski/Karen Thompson, 1986; 1989 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 32)
      - Stonewall 20, 1989 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 33)
      - Stonewall 25, 1994 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 34)
      - Stonewall 25 International March & Rally, New York City - Presenter name tag, 1994 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 35)
      - Stonewall 25 Marshall pass, 1994 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 36)
      - Stonewall 25 - press coverage, 1994 (Oversized 2, Folder 18)
      - T-shirt - A Family of Pride, Palm Beaches, 1993 (Oversized 8, Folder 8)
      - T-shirt - A Family of Pride Worldwide, 1993 (Oversized 8, Folder 9)
      - T-shirt - Lesbian Families: Affirming Our Choices, 1990 Feburary 17-19 (Oversized 8, Folder 6)
      - T-shirt - Lesbian Families: Affirming Our Choices, 1990 Feburary 17-19 (Oversized 8, Folder 7)
      - T-shirt - North Carolina Lesbian & Gay Pride March, Asheville, North Carolina, 1992 June 13 (Oversized 8, Folder 2)
      - T-shirt - Pride Without Borders, Nashville, 1996 (Oversized 8, Folder 5)
      - T-shirt - San Diego Lesbian and Gay Pride 20th Anniversary, Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 11)
      - T-shirt - San Diego Lesbian and Gay Pride 20th Anniversary, Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 12)
      - T-shirt - San Diego Lesbian and Gay Pride 20th Anniversary, Undated (Oversized 8, Folder 13)
      - T-shirt - Soar: A Celebration of Life, Strengthening Our AIDS Response, Undated (Box 22 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 1)
      - Texas Lesbian Conference - Name tag, 1988 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 37)
      - The War Conference, 1988 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 38)
      - Women in Prison, 1981; 1986-1989; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 39)
      - Women's International Resource Exchange, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 40)
      - Women's Pentagon Action, 1981 (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 41)
      - Women's Pentagon Action, 1981 (Oversized 4, Folder 10)
      - Women's Studies, 1976; 1978; 1981; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 42)
      - Women's Rights, 1980-1981; 1983-1989; 1991-1995; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 43)
      - Women Strike for Peace, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (1.1.3-Activism - Other), Folder 44)
      - Women Strike for Peace, 1980-1981; 1984-1988; 1992; 2000; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 11)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1985-1998, Undated; 1.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains correspondence, fliers, informational packets, promotional material and other publications.
    - Anti-Violence, 1987; 1988; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 45)
    - Button with keychain, Undated (Box 30 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Campaign for Fairness in Entertainment, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, 1992; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 47)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 48)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 49)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 50)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 51)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 52)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 53)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 54)
    - Creating Change Conference - name tag, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 55)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1996 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 56)
    - Creating Change Conference, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 57)
    - Creating Change Conference, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 58)
    - Creating Change Conference name tags - panelist, host committee, stage crew, 1991; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 59)
    - Creating Change Conference - poster, 1995 (Oversized 4, Folder 12)
    - Creating Change Conference name tags - presenter, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 60)
    - Executive Committee, 1992; 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 61)
    - Fact sheets, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 62)
    - Federal Legislative Report, ca. 1991 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 63)
    - Gays, Lesbians and Bisexuals in the Military, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 64)
    - Guide Book, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 65)
    - Invitations, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 66)
    - Peri Jude (Lobbyist) - Business Card, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 67)
    - Lesbian Issues, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 68)
    - "Lift the Ban - Stop Discrimination Action Kit", 1994 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 69)
    - Mailings, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 70)
    - Membership, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 71)
    - National Visibility Campaign for the Gay and Lesbian Vote, 1986-1988 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 72)
    - Newsletters, 1988; 1991-1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 73)
    - Notes, 1993; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 74)
    - "Pervasive Patterns of Discrimination Against Lesbians and Gay Men", 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 75)
    - "Political Action Packet on State-Mediated Issues", ca. 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 76)
    - Posters - "Leading the Fight for Freedom", Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 6)
    - Posters - "Leading the Fight for Freedom", Undated (Oversized 5, Folder 7)
    - Presidential Transition, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 77)
    - Press Coverage, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 78)
    - Press Coverage, 1990; 1991 (Oversized 4, Folder 13)
    - Press List, 1993; 1994 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 79)
    - Press Releases, 1988-1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 80)
    - Privacy Project, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 81)
    - Publicity, 1987; Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 82)
    - Resources, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 83)
    - Staffing, 1988; 1992-1994 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 84)
    - Stand Up For Your Rights, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 85)
    - Strengths and Weaknesses Survey, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 86)
    - "Washington, D.C. Lesbian and Gay Communities Portion of Metropolitan Police Department's HR Training Program", 1985 (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 87)
    - Writings, Undated (Box 2 (1-Activism), Folder 88)
  - National Lesbian Conference, 1973-1994, Undated; 1.3; 1.75 cubic ft.
    This subseries consists of Planning drafts, handwritten notes, meeting minutes, administrative material, and correspondence concerning Michelle Crone's central role in organizing the National Lesbian Conference held in Atlanta in 1991.
    - Agenda, draft, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 1)
    - Agenda '89: Women's Legislative Conference, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 2)
    - ALICE (Interim Task Committee), 1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 3)
    - Atlanta Civic Center, 1989-1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 4)
    - Atlanta Meetings, 1989; 1990 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Background Materials, 1979; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Biographies, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 7)
    - Button - Bring Sharon Home, Committee to Free Sharon Kowalski, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 8)
    - Cassette Tape - Susan McHale SkyeDancer, Lesbian Nation: One Nation Among Many, 1991 (Cassette 1)
    - Concert - Washington Sisters, Lea Delaria, Karen Williams, Teresa Trull, 1991 (Vhs 2)
    - Conference Weekend Extravaganza of Comedy Song and Dance, 1991 (Oversized 7, Folder 1)
    - Contact Lists, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 9)
    - Contact Lists: Organizations, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 12)
    - Cost-sharing, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 13)
    - Durham Meeting 3/89, 1989 (3.5in-floppy 1)
    - Entertainment, 1989; 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 14)
    - Events, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 15)
    - Feathers, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 16)
    - Finances, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 17)
    - First National Planning Meeting, Durham, NC, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 18)
    - First National Planning Meeting, Durham, NC - raw video recording of fishbowl sessions, consensus building (2 hours, 3 minutes) (Vhs 3)
    - Fundraising, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 19)
    - International Lesbian Information Service Conference, 1985 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 20)
    - Lesbian International Visibility (LIV) Conference, 1986 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 21)
    - Lesbian Network, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 22)
    - Mailings, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 23)
    - Media Committee, 1989; 1990 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 24)
    - Mobilization/Networking Committee, ca. 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 25)
    - Moon Phases, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 26)
    - Nametag, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 27)
    - National Lesbian Conference Organizing Kit, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 28)
    - National Lesbian Feminist Agenda Conference Planning Meeting, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 29)
    - National Lesbian Rights Conference, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 30)
    - National Lesbian Rights Conference, San Diego - name tag and button, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 31)
    - Notes, 1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 32)
    - Notes, fliers and forms, 1990-1991 (Oversized 4, Folder 14)
    - Notes on slides, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 33)
    - Novelty fan - I am an NLC Fan, Diversity, Solidarity, Empowerment, ca. 1991 (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 6)
    - Nurturing Committee, ca. 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 34)
    - Old Women, 1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 35)
    - Other Conferences, 1980; 1983; 1985-1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 36)
    - Outcomes of the Conference, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 37)
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 38)
    - Poster, 1991 (Oversized 4, Folder 15)
    - Press Coverage, 1988; 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 39)
    - Press Coverage, newspapers, 1989; 1991 (Oversized 4, Folder 16)
    - Press Coverage, newspapers, 1989; 1991 (Oversized 4, Folder 17)
    - Press Information, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 40)
    - Press Releases, 1990; 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 41)
    - Program, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 42)
    - Program Committee, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 43)
    - Proposals, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 44)
    - Publicity, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 45)
    - Queer Nation/NY Panel & Discussion, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 46)
    - Regional Planning, 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 47)
    - Registration Forms, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 48)
    - Schedules/Timelines, 1990; 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 49)
    - Second National Planning Meeting, Portland, OR, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 50)
    - Staffing, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 51)
    - Steering Committee, ca. 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 52)
    - Structure, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 53)
    - T-shirt - National Lesbian Conference Atlanta, 1991 (Box 25 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Third National Planning Meeting, Kansas City, MO, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 54)
    - Travel and Accommodations, 1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 55)
    - Two-Spirited, Thunder People, 1994 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 56)
    - Volunteer Form, 1991 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 57)
    - West Coast Lesbian Conference, 1973 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 58)
    - Women of Color/Racism, 1980; 1989-1991; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 59)
    - Women with Disabilities, 1985; 1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 60)
    - Writings, Undated (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 61)
  - National March on Washington, 1987, 1979-1989, Undated; 1.4; 2.3 cubic ft.
    Alphabetical by subject. Records of the civil disobedience action at the Supreme Court are specifically labeled "Civil Disobedience at the Supreme Court."
    This subseries consists of material relating to the 1987 national march, including material about civil disobedience, and records from Michelle Crone's position as National Civil Disobedience Coordinator and "Out ? Outraged," the 1987 act of civil disobedience at the Supreme Court. Present are correspondence, notes, meeting minutes and memoranda from the committees planning the march. Also included are ephemera, leaflets, pamphlets, newsletters, fliers, and other published material from the March organization. Michelle Crone also collected newspaper clippings and articles pertaining to the march which can be found in the “Press Coverage” folders.
    - A Time to Shine, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 62)
    - AIDS/PWA Information, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 63)
    - Awards, 1987; 1988 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 64)
    - Banner - National March on Washington for Gay and Lesbian Rights, October 11, 1987, "For Love and For Life, We're Not Going Back" (36in by 60in) (Roll 4, Folder 1)
    - Business Cards, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 65)
    - Buttons - 1987 National March on Washington (Box 24 (1-Activism), Folder 5)
    - Civil Disobedience: Background Materials, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 66)
    - Civil Disobedience: The Civilian Complaint Review Board, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 67)
    - Civil Disobedience: Handbooks, 1979; 1980; 1982; 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 68)
    - Civil Disobedience: "Resource Packet for Non-Violent Training", 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 69)
    - Civil Disobedience: War Resisters League Training Packet, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 70)
    - Civil Disobedience: Writings & Publications, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 71)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Check-in Packet, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 72)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 73)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Evaluation Meeting, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 74)
    - Civil Disobedience at Supreme Court: Grievances Filed, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Activism), Folder 75)